BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 4) 6178/004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 4)
1950-1998
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United States Department of Labor
Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS)
6178/004
10.5 cubic feet
10.5 linear ft.
Records (documents), collective labor agreements.
5833597
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 28, 2005
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 18, 2016
Biographical / Historical
The US Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS) was established in 1884 to collect information about employment and labor in the United States. As mandated by the 1947 Taft-Hartley Act, the BLS was formally tasked with responsibility for soliciting, collecting, and analyzing collective bargaining agreements (CBAs) from public and private establishments, and making the agreements publicly available. In the early 1980s, this was function was limited to union contracts made with employers of 1000 or more employees.
In 2002, the National Archives and Records Administration authorized the BLS to donate inactive, non-confidential agreements which were 5 years or more past their expiration date to the Kheel Center where they would be preserved and made available to the public. The Office of Labor-Management Services took over responsibility for collecting and analyzing CBAs in 2011, and continues this donor relationship with the Kheel Center.
Scope and Contents
The US Department of Labor Historical Collective Bargaining Agreements Collection, 6178, is made up of 21 series of expired public- and private-sector collective bargaining agreements dating from 1887 to 2003 and totals 685 linear feet plus 10 CDs of digitized documents and 320 reels of microfilm. In addition to the CBAs, a small volume of related documents such as union constitutions, pension and health plans submitted to the BLS, are also available.
Selected collective bargaining agreements from this collection were digitized with generous funding from the National Historic Publications and Records Commission (NHPRC), and the National Science Foundation (NSF). Because documents other than collective bargaining agreements were also collected and preserved here by the US Department of Labor, a folder containing material that has been digitized, may also contain material which has not been digitized such as constitutions, bylaws, working rules, life insurance plans, or other organizational documents. For access to non-digitized material, contact Kheel Center staff.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6178/001: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 1) 6178/002: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 2) 6178/003: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 3) 6178/006: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 6) 6178/007: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 7) 6178/008: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 8) 6178/009: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 9) 6178/010: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 10) 6178/011: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 11) 6178/012: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 12) 6178/013: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 13) 6178/014: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 14) 6178/015: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 15) 6178/016: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 16) 6178/017: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 17) 6178/018: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 18) 6178/019: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 19) 6178/020: OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 20) 6178/021(d): BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 21) Digital 6178/022 mf: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 22) on Microfilm 6178/023: OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 23)
Arrangement
Series I: Industry Code #11, Agriculture, Forestry, Fishing and Hunting
Series II: Industry Code #22, Utilities
Series III: Industry Code #31, Manufacturing
Series IV: Industry Code #32, Manufacturing
Series V: Industry Code #33, Manufacturing
Series VI: Industry Code #42, Wholesale Trade
Series VII: Industry Code #44, Retail Trade
Series VIII: Industry Code #48, Transportation and Warehousing
Series IX: Industry Code #51, Information
Industrial relations -- United States; Collective labor agreements -- United States.; United States. Department of Labor.; United States. Bureau of Labor Statistics.; United States. Bureau of Labor Statistics. Division of Industrial Relations -- Archives; United States. Bureau of Labor Statistics. Office of Wages and Industrial Relations -- Archives
5833597
- Series I: Industry Code #11, Agriculture, Forestry, Fishing and Hunting
  - Code no.1000: Weyerhaeuser Company and International Woodworkers of America, Local 3-536,3-11, 1959-1969 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Code no.1005: Simpson Timber Company and International Woodworkers of America, Local 3-38, 1969-1973 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Series II: Industry Code #22, Utilities
  - Code no.1608: General Electric Company and Hanford Atomic Metal Trades Council, 1960-1967 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Code no.1609: Goodyear Atomic Corporation and Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 10-689, 1960-1963 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Series III: Industry Code #31, Manufacturing
  - Code no.241: Milk Products Manufacturers Association of California and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Joint Council 38, 1961- 1962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Code no.242: Niagara Frontier Unionized Milk Dealers Association and Milk, Ice Cream Drivers and Dairy Employees' Local 39, Buffalo, NY, 1959- 1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Code no.243: Pet Milk Company, Dairy Division and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 23, 1961-1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Code no.245: Alaska Salmon Industry, Inc. and International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union, Local 37, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Code no.246: Associated Producers and Packers, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1968-1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Code no.248: Blue Lake Packers, Inc. of Salem and Corvallis, Oregon and Cannery Warehousemen, Food Processors, Drivers and Helpers, Local 670, 1967-1970 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Code no.249: Los Angeles County Harbor District and Cannery Workers Union of the Pacific, AFL-CIO, 1959-1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Code no.250: California Packing Corporation and Fruit and Vegetable Packers and Warehousemen's Union, Local 760, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Code no.251: California Packing Corporation, Midwest Division, Plants 109,110,111,112 and Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union, AFL-CIO, Local 17, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Code no.252: Del Monte Corporation, Plants 126 and 127 and Cannery Warehousemen, Food Processors, Drivers and Helpers, Locals 670 and 809, 1961-1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Code no.253: California Processors, Inc. and California State Council of Cannery and Food Processing Unions, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1960-1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Code no.257: Duffy-Mott Company, Inc. and Cannery and Preserve Workers' Union, Local 22006, 1959-1962 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Code no.259: H.J. Heinz Company, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania and Canning and Pickle Workers Union, Local 325, 1968-1972 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Code no.263: Seabrook Farms, Co. and Amalgamated Food and Allied Workers Union, AFL-CIO, Local 56, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Code no.264: Stokely-Van Camp, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Locals 56,563,662,695, 1961-1967 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Code no.265: Corn Products Co. and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Locals 7-662,5-617,4,343,7-507, 1961- 1972 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Code no.266: Flour, Feed and Cereal Employers' Association and Pacific Council of Grain Millers, AFL-CIO, 1960-1963 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Code no.268: General Mills, Inc. and American Federation of Grain Millers, AFL-CIO, 1969-1972 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Code no.271: Pillsbury Company, Atchison, Kansas and American Federation of Grain Millers, AFL-CIO, Local 76, 1969-1975 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Code no.273: Clinton Corn Processing Company and American Federation of Grain Millers, Local 6, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Code no.275: Detroit Bakery Employers' Labor Council and Detroit Bakers' Union, Factory Local 326, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Code no.276: Employers of the Metropolitan Area of Washington, D.C. and Backers Local Union, Local 118, 1967-1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Code no.279: Philadelphia Bakery Employers and Food Driver Salesman, Dairy and Ice Cream Workers, Local 463, 1959-1971 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Code no.284: Seattle Bakers' Bureau, Inc. and Bakery Salesmen's Local Union 227, 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Code no.287: Specialty Bakery Owners of America, Inc. and Bakery and Confectionery Workers International Union of America, Local 51, 1954- 1956 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Code no.291: American Crystal Sugar Company and American Federation of Grain Millers, AFL-CIO, 1965-1971 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Code no.292: American Sugar Refining Company and United Packinghouse Workers of America, Local 1101, 1959-1962 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Code no.294: California and Hawaiian Sugar Refining Corporation and International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union, Local 6, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Code no.295: California and Hawaiian Sugar Refining Corporation and Sugar Workers Union No 1, Seafarers International Union of North America, AFL-CIO, 1959-1970 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Code no.297: American Crystal Sugar Company; Holly Sugar Co.; Spreckels Sugar Company and Distillery, Rectifying, Wine and Allied Workers International Union; United Sugar Workers Council of California, 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Code no.298: Michigan Sugar Company and International Council of Sugar Workers and Allied Industries Unions, AFL-CIO, 1959- 1971 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Code no.299: National Sugar Refining Company and Sugar Refinery Workers' Local 1648, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Code no.300: Sugar Companies Negotiating Committee and Negotiating Committee of International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union, Local 142, 1969-1974 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Code no.301: Utah-Idaho Sugar Company and American Federation of Grain Millers, Local s 276,281,289,320, 1967-1970 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Code no.302: Confectioners Industrial Relations Board, Inc. and Candy and Confectionery Workers Union, Local 452, 1961-1972 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Code no.304: Planters Peanuts and Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union Local 26, 1966-1971 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Code no.308: Brewery Proprietors of Milwaukee, Wisconsin and Brewery Workers Local 9, 1961-1973 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Code no.309: California Brewers Association and Teamster Brewery and Soft Drink Workers Joint Board of California, 1960-1970 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Code no.310: Schenley Distillers, Inc. and Distillery Workers Local 266, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Code no.311: Anheuser-Bush, Inc. and International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers of America, AFL-CIO, Local 187, 1960-1969 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Code no.312: Brewing Companies and International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers of America, AFL-CIO, Locals 22,67,144, 1960-1966 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Code no.313: Theo. Hamm Brewing Company, St. Paul, Minnesota and Brewery Workers Locals 343, 97, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Code no.2103: Auburn Shoe Manufacturers Association and Lewiston-Auburn Shoeworkers Protective Association, 1960-1969 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Code no.2111: J.F. McElwain Co. and New Hampshire Shoe Workers Union of Manchester, 1959-1972 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Code no.2118: Chicago Luggage and Leather Goods Manufacturers Assoc. and Luggage Workers Union of Chicago, Local 415L, 1960- 1969 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Code no.2120: Leather and Leather Products, Leather Novelty Companies in New York and Pocketbook and Novelty Workers Union, New York, Local 1, 1959-1968 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Code no.2121: New York Industrial Council of the National Authority for the Ladies' Handbag Industry and Pocketbook and Novelty Workers Union, New York, 1959-1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Code no.2122: Weinbrenner Division of Textron, Inc. and Boot and Shoe Workers Union, Locals 688,717,687, 1959-1966 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Code no.2125: Samsonite Corporation and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, Local 724, 1967-1970 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Code no.2125-2: Shwayder Brothers, Inc. and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, Local 724, 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Code no.2127: Tanners Association of Fulton County, Inc. and Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, Local 1712, 1967-1972 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Code no.2129: Block Cut Manufacturers, Inc. and Consolidated Glove Cutters and Shavers Union, Local 1714, 1969-1972 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Code no.202: Packers and Sausages Manufacturers Association and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 100, 1967-1970 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Code no.203: Cudahy Company and United Packinghouse Food and Allied Workers, AFL-CIO, 1967-1970 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Code no.205: Dubuque Packing Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 150, 1960- 1970 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Code no.207: Geo. A. Hormel and Co. and United Packinghouse Food and Allied Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 9, 1967-1969 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Code no.208: Hygrade Food Products Corporation and United Packinghouse Workers of America, AFL-CIO, Locals 69,127,231,329,169,117, 1959-1970 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Code no.210: Oscar Mayer and Co. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 431, 1961-1967 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Code no.211: Oscar Mayer and Co. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 538, 1961-1967 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Code no.213: Independent Meat Packers of Los Angeles County, California and Butcher's Union, Local 563, 1959-1970 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Code no.221: Swift and Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, 1961-1970 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Code no.222: Swift and Company and United Packinghouse, Food and Allied Workers, AFL-CIO, 1961-1970 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Code no.223: Wilson and Co. and United Packinghouse, Food and Allied Workers, AFL-CIO, 1961-1967 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Code no.228: Dairy Industry Industrial Relations Association and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1970-1973 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Code no.229: Good Humor Corporation and Ice Cream Drivers and Employees Union, Local 757, 1965-1968 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Code no.230: Milk, Ice Cream and Dairy Industry, Pittsburgh and Vicinity and Milk and Ice Cream Salesmen, Drivers and Dairy Employees, Local 205, 1967-1970 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Code no.231: Alexandria, Embassy and Thompson Dairies and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 246, 1966-1971 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Code no.233: Milk and Ice Cream Employers and Joint Council of Teamsters No. 38, 1961-1968 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Code no.234: New York City Ice Cream Industry Employers and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 757, 1957-1968 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Code no.236: Detroit Milk Companies and United Dairy Workers, Local 83, AFL-CIO, 1959-1963 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Code no.237: Milk Dealers, Philadelphia and Vicinity and Food Driver Salesmen, Dairy and Ice Cream Workers Union, Local 463, 1965- 1971 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Code no.239: Northern California Dairy Industry Labor Relations Association and Milk Drivers and Dairy Employees, Local 226, 1961- 1964 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Code no.876: Greater Blouse, Skirt and Neckwear Contractors' Association, Inc. and Joint Board of Cloak, Suit, Skirt and Reefer Makers' Unions, Local 23-25, 1967-1970 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Code no.878: Jonathan Logan, Inc. and International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1966-1969 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Code no.879: Greater Blouse, Skirt, and Undergarment Association, Inc. and Blouse, Skirt and Sportswear Workers Union, Local 23-25, 1967- 1970 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Code no.886: Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Association and Kansas City Joint Board of the International Ladies' Garment Workers Union, 1966-1969 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Series IV: Industry Code #32, Manufacturing
  - Code no.2301: Libbey-Owens-Ford Glass Company and United Glass and Ceramic Workers of North America, AFL-CIO, CLC, 1965- 1970 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Code no.2303: Anchor Hocking Glass Corp. Plants 1 and 2 and American Flint Glass Workers' Union of North America, AFL-CIO, 1961- 1971 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Code no.2304: Anchor Hocking Glass Corp. Plants 1 and 2 and Glass Bottle Blowers Association, 1960-1962 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Code no.2305: Ball Brothers Company, Inc. and United Glass and Ceramic Workers of North America, AFL-CIO, CLC, Local 93, 1959- 1962 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Code no.2306: Brockway Glass Company, Inc. and Glass Bottle Blowers Association, 1960-1962 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Code no.2308: Corning Glass Works and American Flint Glass Workers' Union of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 1000, 1960-1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Code no.2310: Federal Glass Company and American Flint Glass Workers' Union of North America, AFL-CIO, Locals 137,151,596,601,603,605, 1959-1971 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Code no.2311: Glass Container Manufacturers Institute, Inc. and Glass Bottle Blowers Association, 1960-1971 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Code no.2313: Glass Container Manufacturers Institute, Inc. and American Flint Glass Workers' Union of North America, AFL-CIO, 1961- 1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Code no.2314: Knox Glass, Inc. and Glass Bottle Blowers Association, 1960-1968 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Code no.2315: Kimble Glass Company and American Flint Glass Workers Union, AFL-CIO, 1961-1971 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Code no.2316: Owens-Illinois Glass Company and Glass Bottle Blowers Association, 1960-1962 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Code no.2317: Owens-Illinois Glass Company and Glass Bottle Blowers Association, Locals 106-245, 1960-1974 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Code no.2318: Thatcher Glass Manufacturing Co. and Glass Bottle Blowers Association, 1960-1962 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Code no.2321: Huron Portland Cement Co. and United Stone and Allied Products Workers of America, Local 135, 1961-1967 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Code no.2326: Mosaic Tile Company and United Glass and Ceramic Workers of North America, Zanesville Tile Local 79, 1958-1961 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Code no.2327: United States Ceramic Tile Company and United Glass and Ceramic Workers of North America, Local 37, 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Code no.2335: Johns-Manville Products Co. and United Papermakers and Paperworkers, Local 800, 1960-1970 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Code no.2336: Johns-Manville Products Co. and International Chemical Workers Union, Local 60, 1961-1971 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Code no.2337: Minnesota Mining and Manufacturing Company, St. Paul, Minnesota and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 6-75, 1959-1967 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Code no.2338: Norton Company and United Papermakers and Paperworkers, Local 17, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Code no.2339: Owens-Corning Fiberglas Corporation and Glass Bottle Blowers Association, Local 244, 1960-1972 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Code no.2340: Glass Container Manufacturers Institute, Inc. and Glass Bottle Blowers Association, Miami Beach, Florida, 1962-1971 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Code no.2342: Independent Table and Art Glassware Manufacturing Plants and American Flint Glass Workers' Union of North America, AFL-CIO, 1959-1965 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Code no.2344: California Cement Companies and United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union, AFL-CIO, Locals 48,49,52,89,192,296,349,372,405,471, 1971-1973 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Code no.2347: Owens-Corning Fiberglas Corporation and Building and Construction Trades Council of Kansas Cities and Metropolitan Area, AFL-CIO, 1963-1972 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Code no.2349: American-St. Gobain Corporation and United Glass and Ceramic Workers of North America, AFL-CIO, CLC, Locals 10,17,21, 1964-1966 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - The Mead Corporation, 1963-1970 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Nekoosa-Edwards Paper Company (NEPCo), 1969-1973 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Nekoosa-Edwards Paper Company (NEPCo), 1960-1966 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - The Northwest Paper Company, 1962-1969 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Olin Mathieson Chemical Corporation, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers, 1967-1972 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Rheinlander Paper Company, St. Regis Paper Company, 1962-1964 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Rheinlander Paper Company, St. Regis Paper Company, 1962-1969 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Riegal Paper Company, 1959-1971 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Eastern Fine Paper and Pulp Division, Standard Packaging Corporation, 1961-1965 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Eastern Fine Paper and Pulp Division, Standard Packaging Corporation, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Thilmany Pulp and Paper Company, Division of Hammermill Paper Co., 1966-1972 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Thilmany Pulp and Paper Company, Division of Hammermill Paper Co., 1962-1966 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - West Virginia Pulp and Paper Company, 1959-1964 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - West Virginia Pulp and Paper Company, 1965-1970 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - West Virginia Pulp and Paper Company, 1958-1962 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - West Virginia Pulp and Paper Company, 1963-1966 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - West Virginia Pulp and Paper Company, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Brown Company and Sutherland Division of the KVP Sutherland Paper Company, 1965-1971 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Sutherland Division of the KVP Sutherland Paper Company, 1961-1965 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Waldorf Paper Products Company, Hoerner Waldorf Corporation, 1962-1968 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Continental Can Company, 1961-1963 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Continental Can Company, 1964-1966 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Sealright-Oswego Falls Corporation, 1960-1962 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Sealright-Oswego Falls Corporation, 1965-1968 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Union Bag-Camp Paper Company, 1959-1968 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Wall Paper Manufacturing Industry Institute, 1960-1964 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - The Box Association of America, 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - The Box Association of America, 1960-1962 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Continental Can Company, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Container Corporation of America, 1959-1971 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Crown Zellerbach Corporation, 1961-1970 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Fair Trade Paper Box Employers Association, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Fair Trade Paper Box Employers Association, 1960-1962 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, 1958-1970 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - The Mead Corporation, 1961-1967 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - The Mead Corporation, 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Packaging Corporation of America, 1966-1972 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - The Celotex Corporation, 1961-1964 (Box 4, Folder 39)